export const questionsAnswers = [{
  question: 'What is the difference between var, let, and const?',
  answer: 'In JavaScript, var is function-scoped and can be re-declared; let and const are block-scoped with let allowing re-assignment and const preventing it. However, const objects can have their contents modified.'
}, {
  question: 'How was your day?',
  answer: 'It was good, thank you!'
}, {
  question: 'How many times have you eaten bread in your life?',
  answer: 'How many time have you breathed in and out?'
}, {
  question: 'What do you think about birds?',
  answer: 'Birds are cool'
}, {
  question: 'Do you like jumping?',
  answer: 'Jumping jacks!'
}, {
  question: 'If I had 10 apples and Marty took 5, how many apples do I have?',
  answer: 'I have 5 apples!'
}, {
  question: 'How heavy is a kilogram of feathers?',
  answer: 'Same weight as a kilogram of steel'
}, {
  question: 'How many questions does this page have?',
  answer: 'I hope not too many'
}, {
  question: "What's the big deal about yellow baloons?",
  answer: 'They are yellow and they are baloons'
}, {
  question: 'If you know something, would you tell it?',
  answer: 'Depends on something'
}, {
  question: 'How old is the oldest television?',
  answer: 'oldestTv.age'
}, {
  question: 'Do you think this dress is making me look fat?',
  answer: '...'
}, {
  question: 'Cats or dogs?',
  answer: 'Why not both?'
}, {
  question: 'Do you like baseball?',
  answer: 'Only in Japan'
}, {
  question: 'How much sleep do you need?',
  answer: 'More than I have right now'
}, {
  question: 'What is the angle of a 90 degree angle?',
  answer: 'Depends on a 90 degree angle'
}, {
  question: 'What is stronger, brick house or a cement house?',
  answer: 'Next question please'
}, {
  question: 'Do you get wetter if you walk or run under the rain?',
  answer: 'What kind of rain?'
}, {
  question: 'Are wi-fi signal waves visible?',
  answer: "Only when wi-fi does'nt work"
}, {
  question: 'How do you like your steak?',
  answer: 'Well done'
}]